JASPERS JORDI

Contact

Address:

Berkenlaan 8, 3620 Gellik, Limburg, Belgium

Phone:

+32 471 45 64 35

Email:

JordiJaspers@gmail.com

LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/jordijaspers/

Github:

https://github.com/Jordi-Jaspers

Languages

Dutch - Native Language

English - Fluent

French - Advanced

German - Basics

Korean - Basics

Coding languages

Java, Labview
Automation and logic design

Python

RESTful APIs & automation

Verilog & VHDL FPGA programming

Low level C & C++
Basics & Arduino experience

Laravel, HTML & CSS basic web design

MySQL Database experiences

Vue.js, Javascript web development & design

Docker services container technologies

Amazon Web Services

Never the greatest student at school, but I love creating/learning through projects that interest me. Over the years I have taught myself multiple new things. I have spent a lot of time developing software & building electronic circuits. To fund my studies and projects, I work full-time next to my education. I've been catering and working in techrelated businesses since 2010. These different jobs have given me experience in multiple different sectors.

EDUCATION

2020 - 2021

Master's thesis in Electronic & Software engineering, Hanyang University | *Ansang, Seoul, Korea*

Exchange program

2019 - 2021

Masters of Electronic & Software Engineering, Uhasselt/KULeuven | *Diepenbeek, Limburg*

2018 - 2019

Bachelor's thesis in Electronic & Software engineering, Uhasselt/KULeuven | Diepenbeek, Limburg

2015 - 2019

Bachelor of Electronic & Software Engineering, Uhasselt/KULeuven | *Diepenbeek, Limburg*

2009 - 2015

High School Engineering Degree, Technical Institute Sparrendal | Gellik, Limburg

CERTIFICATIONS

Sin Moo Hapkido:

o 3th dan Black Belt - Official Trainer

Technical Institute Sparrendal:

- o VCA Certificate Safety On The Workfloor
- o ICT Certificate Usage Of MS Office
- o Secondary Education Certificate Engineering Science
- o PXL nomination Tech Award 2015

LIMTECH:

Basic Hydraulics & Pneumatics Certificate

UHasselt/KULeuven:

- o Bachelor's Degree in Electronic & Software Engineering
- o Master's Degree in Electronic & Software Engineering

Amazon:

o Multiple Amazon Web Services certificates

WORK EXPERIENCE

08/2014 - ...

Sales Manager, What A Waffle | Maasmechelen, Limburg Student job:

- Improved language skills: French, English
- Improved social skills and cultural intelligence
- Team Management
- Product Inventory

04/2013 - 08/2014

Electrician, Electro Geenard | Gellik, Limburg Student job:

- Developed insight and skill about electrical circuits
- Knowledge through interacting with other engineers

03/2010 - 03/2013

Salesman, Lacoste - Outlet | Maasmechelen, Limburg Student job:

- Communicating with clients in general
- Improved social
- Improved language skills.

VOLENTEERING EXPERIENCE

08/2014 - ...

Martial Arts Instructor, Sin Moo Hapkido | Rekem, Limburg Responsibilities:

- 3th grade black belt instructor
- Imparted key etiquette points, discipline and respect.
- Taught both core principles and fighting techniques to students of all levels.
- Helped students prevent injuries and rendered calm and professional aid in case of accidents.